Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 4 and District 4 Locals, 1935-1991 UE.4.1.4
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 4 Locals, 2.
  - Local 437
    - Local 437 Outgoing Correspondence, January 25, 1941-December 4, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Betzel to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 402 and 437, October 19, 1945; 7.
      - Betzel to Fitzgerald Regarding Kraeuter & Company, July 26, 1946; 8.
      - Betzel to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 437 Strike Request at L.J. Wing Company, May 4, 1948; 9.
      - Betzel to James Matles Regarding Stewards, January 24, 1949; 10.
      - Betzel to Matles Regarding Singer Organization, June 12, 1950; 11.
      - P. Brantley to Emspak, February 5, 1951; 12.
      - Brantley to Matles Regarding Staff, February 28, 1951; 13.
      - Al Burdick to Matles Regarding Salem, MA, Pioneer Electronics, April 20, 1949; 14.
      - Andy De Falcon to Emspak Regarding Dance, May 17, 1943; 15.
      - De Falcon to Matles Regarding Dance with Tickets, May 17, 1943; 16.
      - Henry Goodrich to Emspak Regarding Veterans Initiation Fee Waiver, March 13, 1945; 17.
      - Walter Graczyk to Fitzgerald Regarding Appeal to General Executive Board, October 16, 1947; 18.
      - John Hahn to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, December 5, 1947; 19.
      - Hahn to UE Regarding Bonding, May 26, 1948; 20.
      - Harry Kelner to Emspak Regarding Local 437 Kraeuter Company Strike, November 13, 1953; 21.
      - Kelner to Matles Regarding McCarthyism, December 4, 1953; 22.
      - Ben Markowitz to UE Regarding Officers, May 5, 1942; 23.
      - Markowitz to Emspak Regarding Discrimination Against Negroes and UE Convention Site Charge, September 2, 1942; 24.
      - Markowitz to Emspak Regarding World War II Western Front, September 23, 1942; 25.
    - Local 437 Outgoing Correspondence, December 10, 1940-January 6, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Frank Martienssen to Julius Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Finances, December 10, 1940; 1.
      - Martienssen to Emspak Regarding Per Captia, July 1942; 2.
      - Marie Mauriello to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 3, 1946; 3.
      - Mauriello to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 10-November 13, 1946; 4-6.
      - Mauriello to James McLeish Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 421 and 437, May 12, 1948; 7.
      - Mauriello to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Amalgamation of Locals 421 and 437, June 23, 1948; 8.
      - Mauriello to UE Regarding Newtown Local 437 Coxhead and Carson Strike, March 31, 1949; 9.
      - Mauriello Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Factionalism, November 23, 1949; 10.
      - Frank Murphy to Emspak Regarding Local 437 Kraeuter Strike, October 26, 1953; 11.
      - Murphy to Matles Regarding Membership Meeting, January 6, 1954; 12.
      - Murphy to Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meeting, January 6, 1955; 13.
      - Murphy to Matles Regarding Membership Meeting, January 6, 1955; 14.
      - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Membership Meeting, January 6, 1955; 15.
      - Robert Peterson to Matles Regarding Continental Dynamotor Organization, December 18, 1941; 16.
      - Ernst Pollock to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, December 22, 1941; 17.
      - Pollock to Emspak Regarding Local 437 Sirian Wire Contract, June 4, 1942; 18.
      - Pollock to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 10, 1945; 19.
      - Pollock to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 405 and 437, November 21, 1945; 20.
      - Pollock Telegram to Emspak Regarding Local 437 Newark Transformer Strike, February 25, 1947; 21.
      - Pollock Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 437 East Side Metal Spinning Collective Bargaining, August 27, 1948; 22.
      - Pollock Telegram to Emspak Regarding Local 437 L.J. Wing Strike, April 25, 1948; 23.
      - Pollock Telegram to Emspak Regarding Local 437 Best Manufacturing Strike, August 25, 1949; 24.
      - Pollock to Matles Regarding Baltimore Tenney Engineering and Unemployment, February 23, 1949; 25.
    - Local 437 Outgoing Correspondence, April 14, 1941-May 1, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - Dorothy Scherer to James Matles Regarding Finances, May 1, 1956; 1.
      - John Shuhala Telegram to UE Regarding Local 437 Sirian Wire Strike, April 14, 1941; 2.
    - Local 437 Salary and Expense Letters, Frank Martienssen, February 3-November 18, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Local 437 Finances, 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - Proposed Budget, 1954; 1.
      - Expense Card, May 1, 1956; 2.
      - Finance Committee Report, 1954; 3.
      - Per Capita, 4.
    - Local 437 Amalgamation, October 1-11, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Julius Emspak to Walter Barry, October 1, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Andrew Cameron, October 11, 1945; 2.
    - Local 437 Wichwire Specer, November 2-16, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Julius Emspak to James McLeish, November 2, 1945; 1.
      - McLeish to Emspak, November 16, 1945; 2.
    - Local 437 Marcus Transformer Strike, April 30, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - Al Burdick Telegram to James Matles, April 30, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Burdick, April 30, 1947; 2.
    - Local 437 Inter-union Rivalry and Subsidy, January 15, 1954-August 8, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Memo, January 15, 1954; 1.
      - National Labor Relation Board Election Result, October 18, 1954; 2.
      - Memo, December 20, 1954-April 5, 1955; 3-4.
      - James McLeish to Julius Emspak, August 8, 1955; 5.
    - Local 437 Correspondence, Notifications and Employment List, August 9, 1943-February 5, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Julius Emspak to James McLeish Regarding Foote Presson Separate Charter with July 17, 1943, C. Charles Minisi Letter to Emspak, August 9, 1943; 1.
      - James Lustig to David Scribner Regarding Wages and Military Service, September 7, 1944; 2.
      - Michael Quill to Local 437 Regarding Transport Workers Parmelle Cab Organization, March 15, 1945; 3.
      - Termination of Strike Regarding Newark Gear, November 23, 1945; 4.
      - James McLeish to Emspak Regarding Dura Lamp Organization, January 24, 1947; 5.
      - Al Burdick to James Matles Regarding Local 437 Newark Transformer Strike, January 16, 1947; 6.
      - McLeish to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 421 and 437, May 20, 1948; 7.
      - Notificaiton of Pending Disagreement Regarding Screw Machine, July 29, 1948; 8.
      - Matles to Herb Nichol Regarding Baltimore Tenney Engineering Organization, February 28, 1949; 9.
      - Lustig to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 437 Officers, February 5, 1953; 10.
      - Employment List, 11.
    - Local 437 Leafiet, January 16, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Local 438
    - Local 438 Officers Lists, March 10-April 12, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Local 438 Outgoing Correspondence, Carrie Wheat to UE, May 4, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Local 438 Organization, October 1, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Julius Emspak to William Wanko, October 1, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to James McLeish, October 1, 1947; 2-3.
    - Local 438 Wallace Endorsement, January 27-March 2, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - William Wanko to Albert Fitzgerald, January 27, 1948; 1.
      - Fitzgerald to Wanko, March 2, 1948; 2.
    - Local 438 Factionalism, March 3-April 12, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - William Wanko to James McLeish, March 3, 1948; 1.
      - Wanko to Julius Emspak, April 12, 1948; 2.
    - Local 438 Correspondence, Julius Emspak to William Wanko Regarding Finances, March 26, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Local 438 Charter Supplies, October 1, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Local 439
    - Local 439 Contract, July 11, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Local 439 Officers Lists, September 27, 1943-December 13, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Local 439 Incoming Correspondence, December 9, 1941-June 18, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - Neil Brant to Sol Potegal Regarding War Labor Board, April 14, 1942; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Emerick Artz Regarding Mailing List, March 28, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Frank Nevins Regarding Finances, March 2, 1942; 3.
      - Emspak to Potegal Regarding Local 439 Organization, August 6, 1942; 4.
      - Emspak to Potegal Regarding Babcock & Wilcox Organization and Finances, October 22, 1942; 5.
      - Emspak to Potegal Regarding Finances, October 27, 1942-March 9, 1943; 6-8.
      - Emspak to Clifton Cameron Regarding Finances, July 19, 1944; 9.
      - Emspak to Walter Barry Regarding Per Capita, November 6, 1944; 10.
      - Emspak to Cameron Regarding Veterans Dues, June 18, 1945; 11.
      - James Matles to A.W. Chuck Regarding Wages, December 9, 1941; 12.
    - Local 439 Outgoing Correspondence, December 31, 1941-June 14, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Clifton Cameron to Julius Emspak Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 427, 442 and 439, June 14, 1945; 1.
      - Sol Potegal to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, War Labor Board and Factionalism, August 1, 1942; 2.
      - Potegal to UE Regarding Local 439 Collective Bargaining at International Nickel and American Radiator, October 12, 1943; 3.
      - William Speckin to James Matles Regarding Local 439 Babcock & Wilcox Collective Bargaining, December 31, 1941; 4.
    - Local 439 Salary and Expense Letters, Emerick Artz, May 5-November 18, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Local 439 Bonding, December 1941-Mrach 1942 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - Questionnaire, December 1941; 1.
      - Form, December 18, 1941; 2.
      - Questionnaire, March 1942; 3.
    - Local 439 Finances, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Acknowledgement of Liability, February 2, 1943; 1.
      - Reciept, March 10, 1943; 2.
      - Ledger, 1944-1945; 3.
    - Local 439 Collective Bargaining, Januayr 6-8, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - Union Demands, January 6, 1941; 1.
      - Charles Post to James Matles, January 8, 1941; 2.
    - Local 439 War Labor Board Case and Strike, March 23-October 20, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - Neil Brant to Louis Gill, March 23, 1942; 1.
      - War Labor Board Brief, April 13, 1942; 2.
      - Statement by Local 439, May 1942; 3.
      - James McLeish to Julius Emspak, October 20, 1942; 4.
    - Local 439 Bonding, December 19, 1942-March 4, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Samuel Rotnbaid to National Sorety Corporation, December 14, 1942; 1.
      - Albert Olson to Julius Emspak, March 4, 1943; 2.
    - Local 439 Correspondence, December 24, 1940-February 10, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - James Matles Telegram to Andrew Chuck, December 24, 1940; 1.
      - Ernest De Maio to Neil Brant Regarding Baeberton Babcock & Wilcox, Steel Workers Organizing Committee, and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, February 10, 1941; 2.
    - Local 439 Newspaper, The B. and W. Striker, January 15, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Local 439 Newspaper Clipping, "US Acts in Bayonne Strike," Herald Tribune, May 27, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Local 440
    - Local 440 Officers Lists, October 20, 1942-February 12, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 78)
      - Lists, October 20, 1942-November 26, 1946; 1-3.
      - List with John Hutnick Letter to Julius Emspak, February 24, 1947; 4.
      - List, March 10, 1947; 5.
      - List with March 4, 1948, Hutnick Letter to Emspak, March 1948; 6.
      - List, May 6, 1949; 7.
      - List with February 23, 1949, John Kettyle Letter to UE, February 1949; 8.
      - List, February 12, 1949; 9.
    - Local 440 Membership Minutes, September 9, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Local 440 Incoming Correspondence, December 12, 1940-May 9, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 80)
      - Neil Brant to Charles Rannells Regarding Overtime and War Labor Board, May 25, 1943; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Chester Dowdell Regarding Mailing List, December 12-18, 1940; 2-3.
      - Emspak to Herman Rickert Regarding Factionalism, July 2, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Rickert Regarding Finances, September 5-October 14, 1941; 5-7.
      - Emspak to John King Regarding USO, September 25, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak to Richard Townsend Regarding Staff Members, October 25, 1943; 9.
      - Emspak to Lillian Brown Regarding Finances, July 21, 1944; 10.
      - Emspak to Patrick Tuohey Regarding Veterans Dues, July 10, 1945; 11.
      - Emspak to Vincent Mudiak Regarding Finances, August 31, 1945; 12.
      - Emspak to John Kettyle Regarding Dues Check-off, May 9, 1949; 13.
    - Local 440 Outgoing Correspondence, October 29, 1940-June 14, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 81)
      - Michael Capp to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues and Per Capita, June 14, 1949; 1.
      - Anthony DeMaio to James Matles Regarding Mailing List, November 26, 1941; 2.
      - C.H. Dowdell to James Carey Regarding Foster-Wheeler Organization, October 29, 1940; 3.
      - John Hutnick to William Lousdale Regarding Local 440 Foster-Wheeler Strike, April 24, 1947; 4.
      - Hutnick to Emspak Regarding Local 440 Foster-Wheeler Strike, May 29, 1947; 5.
      - John Kettyle to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-off, May 3, 1949; 6.
      - Stephen Krissak to UE Regarding USO, September 10, 1942; 7.
      - Anthony Nagy to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, November 26, 1947; 8.
      - Herman Rickert to UE Regarding Factionalism, July 1, 1941; 9.
      - Rickert to UE Regarding Finances, October 7, 1941; 10.
      - Richard Townsend to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, October 7, 1943; 11.
      - Townsend to National Labor Relations Board Regarding Negotiations, September 14, 1945; 12.
      - Patrick Touhey to Empsak Regarding Staff Members, February 21, 1945; 13.
      - Touhey to Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 5, 1945; 14.
      - Touhey to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 20, 1945; 15.
    - Local 440 Bonding, February-March 1942 (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Questionnaire, February 1942; 1.
      - Form, March 2, 1942; 2.
    - Local 440 Salary and Expense Letter, H. Rickert, May 29, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Local 440 Dowdell Reimbursement, December 24-30, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Neil Brant to Julius Emspak, December 24, 1940; 1.
      - C.H. Dowdell Statement, December 30, 1940; 2.
    - Local 440 Collective Bargaining, William Santora to Eilliam Lonsdale, April 7-May 4, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Local 440 Staff Members, September 1-October 6, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - James Matles to Walter Barry, September 1, 1943; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Barry, October 6, 1943; 2.
    - Local 440 Strike, September 14-November 30, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Richard Townsend to National Labor Relations Board, September 14, 1945; 1.
      - John Daly to Townsend, September 27, 1945; 2.
      - Daly to Albert Fitzgerald, September 27, 1945; 3.
      - Michael Witkosky Letter, 4.
      - Julius Emspak to Walter Barry, November 30, 1945; 5.
    - Local 440 Corresponcence, Report, and Election Data, February 5, 1941-June 20, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Neil Brant to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 440 Officers, February 5, 1941; 1.
      - Foster-Wheeler Financial Report, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Barry Regarding Per Capita, July 16, 1945; 3.
      - William Brown Organizational Report Regarding St. Catherines Foster-Wheeler Organizaiton, 4.
      - Emspak to William Santora Regarding Dues, June 20, 1949; 5.
      - Election Data, 6.
    - Local 440 Newspaper, FW News and 440, September 5-October 22, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Local 440 Newspaper, Employee Association News, October 14, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Local 440 Leaflets, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 91)
      - "To All Workers" Regarding St. Catherines Foster Wheeler Organization, 1947; 1.
      - "Announcing" Regarding St. Catherines Foster Wheeler Organization, September 23, 1947; 2.
      - "Sunday 2 P.M." Regarding St. Catherines Foster Wheeler Organization, September 26, 1947; 3.
      - Withdrawal of Notice Form Regarding National Labor Relation Board, 4.
    - Local 440 Newspaper Clipping, "Congress of Industrial Organization Victory Aids US Metals Local," CIO News, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Local 441
    - Local 441 Phelps Dodge Copper Products Corporation Contracts, May 5, 1941-May 5, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Local 441 Officers Lists, August 2, 1942-August 27, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Local 441 Incoming Correspondence, September 25, 1941-May 2, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 95)
      - Edwin Beal to Locals 933 and 441 Regarding National War Labor Board, May 19, 1942; 1.
      - Beal to Local 441 Regarding NWLB Negotiations, June 25, 192; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Laurie Salerno, September 25, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to Charles MacLaren, March 23, 1942; 4.
      - Emspak to MacLaren Regarding "Recomendations of (UE) General Officers", April 3, 1942; 5.
      - Emspak to Elmer Stafford Regarding Veterans Initiation Fees, April 26-May 3, 1945; 6-7.
      - Emspak to Frank Blujewicz Regarding Possible Strike, November 7, 1945; 8.
      - Emspak to Stafford Regarding Strike Fund, March 18-April 7, 1946; 9-10.
      - Emspak to Wesley Mitchell Regarding Political Action Committee, October 2, 1946; 11.
      - Emspak to MacLaren Regardung Dues, October 10, 1946; 12.
      - Emspak to Theodore Narushof Regarding Strike, February 26, 1947; 13.
      - Emspak to Mitchell Regarding Strike Fund, April 22, 1947; 14.
      - Emspak to Stafford Regarding PAC, January 7, 1948; 15.
      - Emspak to Narushof Regarding Officers, January 13, 1948; 16-17.
      - Emspak to Charles Stewart Regarding PAC, February 6, 1948; 18.
      - Emspak to Grace E. Marks Regarding UE Convention, September 30, 1948; 19.
      - Emspak to Marks Regarding PAC, January 11, 1949; 20.
      - Emspak to George Rettinger Regarding Finances, April 4, 1949; 21.
      - Emspak to Mitchell with April 29, 1949, Emspak Letter to UE Locals Regarding Phelps Dodge and 1946 Local 441 Strike; and April 27, 1949, John Duris Letter to UE Locals Regarding 1946 Mario Russo Strike Expenses, May 2, 1949; 22.
    - Local 441 Incoming Correspondence, May 1, 1941-April 18, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 96)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Wesley Mitchell Regarding Rally, May 2, 1946; 1.
      - Fitzgerald to Mitchell Regarding Local 442 Rally, May 17, 1946; 2.
      - Norma Gould to Joseph Savage, May 1, 1942; 3.
      - James Matles to Local 441 Regarding Phelps Dodge Contract, May 26, 1941; 4.
      - Matles to Laurie Salerno Regarding Staff, August 16-25, 1941; 5-6.
      - Matles to Salerno Regarding Charles MacLaren Union Work and Time Off, December 11, 1941; 7.
      - Matles to MacLaren Regarding Overtime, October 22, 1942; 8.
      - Matles to Mitchell, May 17, 1946; 9.
      - Matles to Mitchell Regarding Local 441 Membership Meeting, February 4, 1947; 10.
      - Matles to Theodore Narushof, December 23, 1947; 11.
      - Don Pinkston to Bert Eckstein Regarding Phelps Dodge History Book, April 18, 1947; 12.
      - Ben Riskin to Mitchell, August 14, 1946; 13.
    - Local 441 Outgoing Correspondence, January 27, 1941-September 28, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 97)
      - Charles Bean to Julius Emspak Regarding Membership, August 28, 1941; 1.
      - Sigmund Bednarski to UE News Regarding Jim Carey Factionalism, Defense Mediation Board and Phelps Dodge Strike, June 10, 1941; 2.
      - Frank Blujewicz to James Matles Regarding Negotiations, November 6, 1945; 3.
      - Charles MacLaren to Wylie Brown Regarding Negotiations, January 5, 1942; 4.
      - MacLaren to Emspak Regarding Local 441 Phelps Dodge War Production Council, March 13, 1942; 5.
      - MacLaren to Emspak Regarding Recomendation of UE General Officers, March 27, 1942; 6.
      - MacLaren to W.J. Palmer Regarding Group Insurance, March 3, 1948; 7.
      - MacLaren to Neil Brant Regarding Arbitration, September 30, 1942; 8.
      - MacLaren to Matles with March 3, 1948, MacLaren Letter to Palmer Regarding Group Insurance, March 4, 1948; 9.
      - MacLaren to Matles with March 5, 1948, Palmer Letter to MacLaren Regarding Group Insurance, March 9, 1948; 10.
      - MacLaren to Matles with MacLaren Letter to Palmer Regarding Negotiations, March 24, 1948; 11.
      - MacLaren to Matles with March 29, 1948, Palmer Letter to MacLaren Regarding Negotiations, March 31, 1948; 12.
      - MacLaren to Matles Regarding Grievance Procedure, August 23, 1948; 13.
      - MacLaren to Wylie Brown, January 5; 14.
      - Grace Marks to Miss Barisa Regarding UE Convention, September 28, 1948; 15.
      - Ernest Martin to Brown Regarding National Labor Relations Board Election, January 27, 1941; 16.
      - Martin to James Carey Regarding Strike, April 7, 1941; 17.
      - Wesley Mitchell, Sr. to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Rally, April 30, 1946; 18.
      - Mitchell to Fitzgerald Regarding Rally, May 9, 1946; 19.
      - Mitchell to Matles, May 10, 1946; 20.
      - Mitchell to Fitzgerald, May 24, 1946; 21.
      - Mitchell to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 25, 1946; 22.
      - Mitchell to Emspak, January 17, 1947; 23.
      - Mitchell to Fitzgerald Regarding Taft-Hartley, January 27, 1947; 24.
      - MacLaren to Palmer Regarding Grievances, May 20, 1942; 25.
    - Local 441 Outgoing Correspondence, August 6, 1941-March 22, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 98)
      - Joseph Mrak to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, March 22, 1949; 1.
      - Theodore Narushef to Emspak Regarding Legal Defense with List of Legal Defense Expenses, February 12, 1947; 2.
      - Narushef to James Matles Regarding Staff, May 8, 1947; 3.
      - Narushef to Local 401 Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, October 6, 1947; 4.
      - Narushef to Matles, December 17, 1947; 5.
      - Narushef to Emspak, January 9, 1948; 6.
      - Al O'Neal to Emspak Regarding Officers, September 9, 1943; 7.
      - Laurie Salerno to Matles Regarding Staff, August 6, 1941; 8.
      - Salerno to Matles Regarding Navy Department Harassment, September 23, 1941; 9.
      - Salerno to Matles Regarding Officers, December 8, 1941; 10.
      - Salerno to Emspak Regarding Local 441 Constitution, December 30, 1941; 11.
      - Salerno to Emspak Regarding Constitution, January 6, 1942; 12.
      - Elmer Stafford to UE Regarding Veterans Initiation Fee Waiver, May 1, 1945; 13.
      - Stafford to Emspak Regarding Local 441 Anti-Injunction Rally, March 27, 1946; 14.
      - Stafford to UE Regarding Supplies and Expenses, October 11, 1946; 15.
      - Stafford to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, December 16, 1947; 16.
      - Joseph Van Savage to Matles Regarding World War II and Anti-Negro Prejudice with April 21, 1942, Van Savage Letter to President Franklin D. Roosevelt Regarding War Policy, April 24, 1942; 17.
      - UE Local 441 to UE Regarding Veterans Stamps, April 23, 1945; 18.
    - Local 441 Bonding Form, March 5-10, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Local 441 Salary and Expanse Letters, Charles Bean, September 9-19, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Local 441 Finances, October 1, 1946-September 5, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 101)
      - UE Voucher, December 23; 1.
      - Local 441 Treasurer Reciepts, September 5, 1948; 2.
      - Political Action Committee Statement, October 1, 1946; 3.
    - Local 441 Strike Organization, December 10, 1940-May 14, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 102)
      - Peter Besch to Wylie Brown, December 10, 1940; 1.
      - Brown to Besch, December 12, 1940; 2.
      - Besch to Brown, December 16, 1940; 3.
      - Brown to Besch, December 26, 1940; 4.
      - Brown to James Carey, December 26, 1940; 5.
      - William Hammalt Davis Telegram to UE, April 9, 1941; 6.
      - Davis Telegram to Julius Emspak, April 28, 1941; 7.
      - Emspak Telegram to Davis, April 28, 1941; 8.
      - James Matles Telegram to Brown, April 30, 1941; 9-10.
      - Brown Telegram to Matles, May 1, 1941; 11.
      - Matles Telegram to Davis, May 1, 1941; 12.
      - Davis Telegram to Matles, May 1, 1941; 13.
      - Matles to Davis, May 14, 1941; 14.
    - Local 441 Strike, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 103)